sabong.net.ph 2006-08-21

# Www.sabong.net.ph Privacy Website and Company Information Cockfighting and Gamefowl in the Philippines

**Warning** : main(/home/httpd/vhosts/Sabong.net.Ph/httpdocs/assets/design/ads.inc): failed to open stream: No such file or directory in **/home/sabong/public_html/assets/design/header.inc** on line **118**

**Warning** : main(): Failed opening '/home/httpd/vhosts/Sabong.net.Ph/httpdocs/assets/design/ads.inc' for inclusion (include_path='.:/usr/lib/php:/usr/local/lib/php') in **/home/sabong/public_html/assets/design/header.inc** on line **118**

At Sabong, we take your right to privacy very seriously. 

### Our privacy policy is simple:

**We protect personally identifiable information that we collect on the website.**

**We do not sell, rent or lease your information to any other party aside from our own internal use to analyze and improve the website.**

Whenever you register for any service requiring personal information, such as the Posting Pit (Bulletin Board), Mailing List, Guest book, e-mail, and other current and future services of Sabong, you will be required to provide any of the following information: your name, email address, zip code, gender, age, member name and password. In addition, you may choose to provide Sabong with additional information, including: your address, household income, education, marital status and employment status. 

Sabong will not sell or reveal to any third party your name, address, email address and member name, period. Sabong allows limited and case by case access to database information by third-parties only in providing technical services, such as email, but only to the extent necessary to provide you with those services. In those instances, the third party is bound by these terms. Your informed consent shall be in the form of an 'opt in' or similar policy. 

Sabong reserves the right to terminate your Bulletin Board and/or your email account if you use these services maliciously, improperly and/or for your commercial gain or other purposes not otherwise allowed by the operators of this website, or if your actions are contrary to the goals and purposes of the operators of this website. 

### Cookies

The Sabong web sites are operated by Rooster Content Online, Inc. Access to the web site is free and anonymous. The privacy of visitors is of paramount importance to us. Certain pages within this web site have the ability to place a cookie on your computer. These cookies serve only to remember information that helps you get to pages and sections of the website that you want to access. An example is the Posting Pit or Message Forum. Cookies are also used to track what pages most users have accessed. Furthermore, our cookies are session variables which self-terminate after you have closed all instance of the browser. 

### Good Internet surfing habits.

When posting through public computers, make sure that you close all browser instances, delete temporary files and clear browser history so the following user cannot pry on your internet activities 

Each web page access is recorded in a log file. The contents of the log file are analyzed each week and each month to determine how many visitors we serve, what pages they access the most, location where they connect from, and other statistical data that help us understand our users, and improve the website experience accordingly. 

### Mailing List

Visitors who add their name to the Mailing List database will receive e-mail from Sabong. You will receive no other unsolicited e-mail from us. Information in the Mailing List, Posting Pit and Guestbook database is not available for sale or other use by anyone outside of Sabong. 

### Posting of Personal Information

Users are forwarned about posting personally identifiable information for general public access on the website. RCOI and Sabong and not responsible for unmitigated access to these information that have been posted by the user. These items include photos showing and identifying persons, contact information such as real names, telephone numbers and addresses. We have provided secure person to person communication facilities for business and confidential transactions, please use them for your own safety. 

### April 2000. Modified June 2003. Keep it Safe Online.
